

PEDRO SANCHEZ

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I'm a Frontend developer, with 2 years of experience using Vue.js.

I am also studying C#/.NET and Python in order to increase my programming knowledge and backend development.

I am learning Unity as well, because game development is something that I always loved.

CONTACT

- +54 9 3548 464913
- ≥ pedrolampo50@gmail.com
- La Falda, Córdoba, Argentina
- /pedrolampo
- in /in/pedrolampo
- www.pedro-sanchez.netlify.app

SKILLS

- Javascript / HTML / CSS
- React Js
- Vue.js
- React Native / Expo
- C# / .NET
- Unity Engine
- Bootstrap
- Git / GitHub / Gitlab
- Rest API's

LANGUAGES

- Advanced English
- Native Spanish
- Basic German

EDUCATION

Physics Degree

Universidad Nacional de Córdoba - 2018 - 2022

COURSES

Python

Coderhouse - May to Aug. 2024

Foundational C# with Microsoft

freeCodeCamp - Apr. to Jun. 2024

React JS

Coderhouse - Oct. to Dec. 2021

Javascript

Coderhouse - Aug. to Oct. 2021

Web Development

Coderhouse - Jun. to Aug. 2021

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Front-End Developer at Viseven

Feb.2022 - Feb.2024

Recommendation Letter (Link)

- HTML5 & CSS3
- JavaScript
- Vue.js
- Salesforce
- Veeva Vault
- eWizard Framework

IT Services at SasitoGames

2015 - 2018

- Technical Support
- DB Maintenance
- Webapp Maintenance